CAM WALLER UX Designer

camcreates.com

 □ cam@camcreates.com camcreates.github.com

(904) 635-7296

I'm an analytical-minded artist with a passion for problem-solving, learning and storytelling in any form. I approach design with creativity, multimedia expertise and years of client management experience to produce solutions that fulfill business needs and deliver superb experiences to their users.

Past Projects

UX DESIGNER - SALTER MITCHELL

Website redesign for the International Rhino Foundation with focus on user research, information architecture and visual design.

GAME ARTIST & ANIMATOR - HORSE ISLE

Designing and producing art assets, animation and UI elements for casual children's Flash games.

Instructional Designer - Social Media Online Class.com

Production of Instagram 101 class, including lesson copy, graphics and tutorial videos, and several additional class updates.

FLASH ANIMATOR & DEVELOPER - DR. MIRACLE'S

Designing and producing a custom Flash "lounge" environment including all backgrounds, character designs, animation and scripting.

Professional Experience

INDEPENDENT CONSULTANT • 2007 - PRESENT

Traveling artist, designer, writer, editor, translator and language tutor

COMMUNITY ORGANIZER • GPHOMESTAY • 2014 - PRESENT

Jacksonville, FL Community Organizer generating host family leads for international students

INTERN - LABO INTERNATIONAL EXCHANGE FOUNDATION • 2012 - 2013

Intern in Nagoya and Fukuoka offices involved in exchange programs and youth groups

EFL TEACHER • TEACH & LEARN WITH GEORGIA • 2010 - 2011

Volunteer English teacher for public schools in rural and urban areas

MANAGING EDITOR • GENXXL • 2010

Managing editor and podcast team manager

CAGE ASSISTANT MANAGER • SAVANNAH COLLEGE OF ART & DESIGN • 2007 - 2008

School of Film and Digital Media equipment cage monitor and assistang manager

Education

GENERAL ASSEMBLY WASHINGTON. DC • 2014 - 2015

User Experience Design Immersive

SAVANNAH COLLEGE OF ART & DESIGN SAVANNAH, GA • 2004-2008

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Animation

Skills

Client Management Art & Design Animation Sketching User Research Wireframes & Prototyping Object-Oriented Programming HTML/CSS

Tools